singer22.com 2011-12-01

# Singer22 Privacy Policy

  | 

**Singer22 Privacy Policy**

Gosi Enterprises, Ltd dba Singer22 ("Singer22" or "We" or "Us") has created this privacy statement (this "Statement") in order to demonstrate its commitment to customer privacy. Privacy on Singer22's website (the "Website") is of great importance to Us. Because We and our third party providers, including, but not limited to, Yahoo!, Facebook and Twitter (collectively "TPPs") may gather important information via the Website from our visitors (collectively "Customer" or "You" or "Your"), We have established this Statement as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices. We reserve the right to change this Statement at any time and will provide notification of any material change on the Website. 

COLLECTED INFORMATION 

We or our TPPs, may require Customers who register to purchase products from our Website, to be on our e-mail list, or generally to use our retail services (collectively, the "Service" or "Services") to give Us or our TPPs contact and other information, which may include but is not limited to Your name, company name, address, phone number, email address, cookies, IP address (collectively "Personal Information"). You can opt out of providing said information by not entering it when asked or not visiting the Website (or not "socializing" with us on any social networks), although not providing it may hinder Your ability to order products from us or use the Services. You can opt out of any correspondence from Us by following the applicable opt out procedures listed on any correspondence, but You should be aware that archival or back-up copies of said Personal Information will not cease to exist and your Personal Information may still be included in the aggregate and in the Singer22 history files. Further, We are under no obligation to remove said information or make any edits to your Personal Information and shall not be held liable for failing to do so nor for any of our TPPs failure to do so. 

We may use the information that we collect to enhance the Services for You. We or our TPPs may also use the information to contact you to further discuss interest in our company, the Website, or in any way that We, in our sole discretion, deem to be reasonable. Your email address and any Personal Information will not be distributed or shared with third parties unless it is to transact such business as You have contracted us to do, to comply with any legal processes and/or law enforcement requests, or in order to conduct business as We, in our sole discretion, deem reasonable. You can opt out of being contacted by Us, or receiving such information from Us, at any time by sending an email to legal@Singer22.com or by using the applicable opt out process. We may also email information regarding updates to the System, Service or company, and may send a customer newsletter, advertisement, or other correspondence. Any opt-out by You is not deemed valid until processed by Us. It is your obligation to verify that you have been opted-out. Singer22 shall not be liable for problems with the opt-out procedures. 

Except as We explicitly state at the time We request information, or as provided for herein or in the Singer22 Terms of Use Agreement, We do not disclose to third parties the information provided. Any billing information you provide Us is not used by Us for marketing or promotional purposes, except as provided for herein. 

THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES 

The Website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. You will need to check the policy statement of these others websites to understand their policies. When you access a linked site you may be disclosing your Personal Information. It is your responsibility to keep such information private and confidential. 

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION 

This Statement is part of the Terms of Use of the Website and any use of the Website is governed by those Terms of Use. Questions regarding this Statement or the practices of Singer22 should be directed to Singer22's Administrator by emailing such questions to legal@Singer22.com or by U.S. mail return receipt requested, addressed to Singer22, Attn: System Administrator, 441 Glen Cove Road, East Hills, NY 11577. 

This policy is effective as of January 1, 2010 

|
